ads1-adnow.com 2016-10-19

# Privacy policy - native advertising

__By using this site, you agree to use cookie files for analytics, personalized content and advertising. More about ourCookie Policy

Adnow.com (hereinafter "Company") is an online advertising platform specializing in providing internet advertising campaigns. To provide Clients with internet advertising services COMPANY uses its own technology platform “Adnow” (hereinafter “Adnow”).

The COMPANY provides access to its Advertisers (the "Clients") to the platform “Adnow”, performing displaying advertising ads to their potential customers – users. The COMPANY may collect anonymised personal data of Users during the process of internet advertising services.

The COMPANY endeavors to safeguard and protects their Users’ information. For better protection of Users’ privacy The COMPANY provides this Privacy Policy regarding the types of collected information, the protection of such information and the ways of “Opt-Out” from any collection of User’s information.

The COMPANY is guided by the following Privacy Policy’s Rules on the collection and protection of information.

1\. COMPANY shall to bring to the Customers’ and Users’ notice the basic rules of “Adnow”, the principles and rules of information processing, the type and amount of information collected by “Adnow.com”.

Under any circumstances The COMPANY does not process personal data of Users except in the case of the direct provision by Users of personal data to contact with the COMPANY.

2\. “Adnow” and Users’ information.

Providing Internet Advertising Services “Adnow” may collect anonymous data of users regarding the IP address of the user’s equipment, the Internet service provider, type, browser language in use, and his version of the operating system installed on user’s equipment, information about user’s visited sites such as the address (URL) is an Internet page that displays information about the user and advertising clicks on them.

Collected by the COMPANY’s platform “Adnow” User Information is the statistical information.

3\. Cookies files.

Cookies are small files that a Adnow.com transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

The COMPANY’s Customers can use their own database, which may contain personal data information. In this case, personal data information is used only by this Customer for targeting their advertising campaigns .

4\. What do The COMPANY uses the information of Users for?

\- To render properly the COMPANY’s services  
\- To improve customer service  
\- To implement targeted display ads.  
\- For the statistical research;  

5\. Confidentiality

The COMPANY shall not pass by any means or/ and under any circumstances received user information to third parties, except for the provision of this information to such third parties, which operates on behalf of the COMPANY and solely for the provision of Internet Advertising Services by Adnow.com. The COMPANY may provide third parties with information about Users in anonymous form only and solely in the cases stipulated by the legislation of the England and Wales.

6\. The right of “Opt-Out”.

Any User has the right to prohibit the COMPANY to collect User’s statistical information via the function «Opt-Out».
